# Arezoo Alipanah

Phone: +989195529919 LinkedIn: <u>arezooalipanah</u>
Email: <u>arzalipanah@gmail.com</u> Github: <u>arezooalipanah</u>

Website: <u>arezooalipanah.netlify.app</u>

I am an experienced programmer with approximately 8 years of working experience with various programming languages and technologies. My journey in programming began with C# while studying in university. Subsequently, I pursued a professional career in front-end development, specialized in JavaScript and related technologies, for about 7 years. Meanwhile, I have also worked among different businesses and acquired valuable insights in front-end development. However, I would like to become a system constructor, I have recently transitioned to Java as it aligns better with my current goals.

Main skills: Java, Spring, Javascript, ReactJS

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Java Developer ~6 months 11/2022 - now

implemented the following 2 projects from scratch with Spring Boot, and connected to the services using feign client: <a href="mailto:authentication-service"><u>authentication-service</u></a>
telepardaz-service

Technologies: Spring (Boot, Data, Security-OAuth2.o, Cloud, Hibernate)

## **Kian Digital** — Senior Front Developer (Tehran Iran)

**2+** years 11/2020 - 12/2022

<u>Bourseon</u>, <u>kiandigital</u>, <u>kiandigital-blog</u>, in the Bourseon project, I implemented a lot of features and ultimately turned it into a CMS that we could quickly use to implement almost all of the company's website.

Develop <u>Dabi</u> project, a sales and consulting platform.

I've started Bourseon-data project from scratch, and its job is to crawl data related to stocks.

Technologies: Javascript, NextJS, Sanic

Contact: Mahsa Jabbari (Manager) - +989367016280

**Maktab Sharif** — Frontend Trainer (Part time)

**~1.5** years 9/2022 - 12/2020

### **Tosan Techno** — Frontend Developer (Tehran Iran)

~1 year 10/2019 - 10/2020

<u>Seller.shopp.market</u>, started from scratch with a backend developer at Shop company, any business can easily turn into an online store with it.

Technologies: Typescript, ReactJS

Contact-linkedin: hamed-farzanefar

## **PersianGig** — Frontend Developer (Tehran Iran)

1+ years 10/2018 - 7/2019

<u>Persiangig</u> is a platform for purchasing cloud infrastructure services.

I implemented its custom design system from scratch.

Technologies: Typescript, ReactJS, Redux

Contact : Amir Yavand Hasani (Manager) - +989129211893

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Golestan University**, Golestan — BSc

9/2009 - 9/2013

Computer Science, Thesis: Implementation of face detection and recognition application with C#.

#### **SKILLS**

Programming Languages Java, JavaScript, TypeScript

FrameWork & Technology Spring (Boot, Data, Security-OAuth2.o, Cloud), Hibernate, Kafka, RabbitMQ

ReactJS, NextJS

DataBase MySql, MongoDB, Redis, H2

Servers Tomcat, nginx

Test Unit Testing (AssertJ, Mockito), Integration Testing (MockMVC)

Build Tools Maven, npm

DevOps & CI/CD Docker, docker-compose, Linux

## Languages

Farsi: native, English: upper intermediate